<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>1</ID>
    <Text>PYE: What a fascinating object! The core seems to repel us, somehow!</Text>
  </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <ParentID>1</ParentID>
    <Text>YARROW: Perhaps the pink liquid is pushing us up?</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>3</ID>
    <ParentID>2</ParentID>
    <Text>CLARY: I somehow doubt that. Normal uplift forces would not be enough to compensate for our weight.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>4</ID>
    <ParentID>3</ParentID>
    <Text>POKE: Hypothesis: The core is composed of a powerful magnet, which is repelling us!</Text>
  </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
    <ID>5</ID>
    <ParentID>4</ParentID>
    <Text>CLARY: That's a silly idea. We aren't charged, the liquid around it isn't charged, and not to mention that such an object would lose its charge over time.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
    <ID>6</ID>
    <ParentID>5</ParentID>
    <Text>PYE: Ah, what if it's from radiation pressure from all the photons emitted by the core?</Text>
  </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
    <ID>7</ID>
    <ParentID>6</ParentID>
    <Text>POKE: It would require a truly enormous amount of luminosity to generate enough radiation pressure to repel us... but it would explain core's unusual brightness.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>8</ID>
    <ParentID>7</ParentID>
    <Text>YARROW: But then why aren't the liquid around it also blown away by this pressure?</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>9</ID>
    <ParentID>8</ParentID>
    <Text>PYE: I'm not sure. Perhaps it has a high adhesive force with whatever material the core is made of?</Text>
  </TextBlock>
    <TextBlock>
    <ID>10</ID>
    <ParentID>9</ParentID>
    <Text>YARROW: And perhaps the innermost layer of liquid was, somehow, travelling towards the core at a high enough velocity to overcome to radiation pressure and stick to it in the first place!</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>11</ID>
    <ParentID>10</ParentID>
    <Text>CLARY: Hmm.. how could it generate such intense luminosity?</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>12</ID>
    <ParentID>11</ParentID>
    <Text>POKE: Perhaps it's a white dwarf - the remains of an extinguished star. Such bodies still retain some of the original star's thermal energy with which it can emit light.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>13</ID>
    <ParentID>12</ParentID>
    <Text>CLARY: That's still not enough... there must be something within its core to continually power it.</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>14</ID>
    <ParentID>13</ParentID>
    <Text>PYE: The path forward is clear then - let's construct a landing pad on the core, so we can investigate this object further!</Text>
  </TextBlock>
  <ShipLogConditions>
    <RevealFact>
      <FactID>Brightdusk_core</FactID>
      <Condition>14</Condition>
    </RevealFact>
  </ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>